{
    "id": "a7d61b27341c44238f45b2cc2bdf6f21",
    "title": "Infinitive With Or Without To",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I was not allowed ………………………",
            "description": "Allow is followed by an infinitive with to.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "to go",
                "going"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Please let him .......................",
            "description": "Let is followed by an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "speak",
                "to speak",
                "speaking"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You ought .................. a doctor.",
            "description": "Ought is followed by a to-infinitive.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "consult",
                "consulting",
                "to consult"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They made me .....................",
            "description": "When made is used in the active voice, it is followed by an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "confess",
                "to confess",
                "confessing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I was made ....................... my right to the property.",
            "description": "When made is in the passive voice, it is followed by an infinitive with to.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "relinquish",
                "to relinquish"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not able …………………………….. this problem.",
            "description": "Be able is followed by an infinitive with to.",
            "answers": [
                "solve",
                "to solve",
                "to solving"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t ………………………….. it anymore.",
            "description": "The infinitive is used without to after modals.",
            "answers": [
                "take",
                "to take",
                "taking"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I forgot .................... the door before going out.",
            "description": "Forget is followed by an infinitive with to.",
            "answers": [
                "lock",
                "to lock",
                "locking"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You don't need ....................... your own device.",
            "description": "When need is used as an ordinary verb, it is followed by an infinitive with to.",
            "answers": [
                "bring",
                "to bring",
                "bringing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You need not ........................ for my drinks.",
            "description": "When need is a modal auxiliary, it is followed by an infinitive with to.",
            "answers": [
                "to pay",
                "pay",
                "paying"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She refused ......................... with the interrogators.",
            "description": "Refuse is followed by an infinitive with to.",
            "answers": [
                "to cooperate",
                "cooperating",
                "cooperate"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I was forced ....................... up my claim.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "give",
                "to give",
                "giving"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}